<resources>
	<string	name="app_name"	translatable="false">Smooth App</string>
    <string name="innocent_test1"><![CDATA[Smooth\'s eng103 app contains detailed procedures complemented with properly scaled diagrams which makes learning eng103 a treat to students. It also contains a large number of exam questions with carefully drafted answers so that the reader becomes well versed with the course. I used it in 100l and it proved it\'s worth therefore i highly recommend it to anyone hoping to Ace Eng103.]]></string>
    <string name="mhiz_testimony3">Using this material has been one of the best things that changed my thoughts about engine drawing. Easy to understand, well organized and defined. Don\'t miss out!!! Sure A is the way... 😁</string>
    <string name="evt_testimony4">I have been in many eng drawing tutorial classes and have used many eng drawing materials, if I\'m to be honest, i must confess that smooth is the best because he has it [Eng drawing] in him like a natural gift. His drawings are always neat, clean and smooth just like his name. He can teach better than the teachers.\nU need smooth materials and tutorial classes to smash Eng 103 And 104\nA trial will convince you. </string>
    <string name="ezeh_testimony5">Smooth is a really a wonderful tutor who knows how to break down Engineering Drawing to any level of understanding. I am happy to be part of his tutorials which helped me alot in my 100lvl.</string>
    <string name="cynt_testimony6">See me dat don\'t sabi Eng drawing but with Smooth\'s assignment solutions and material, I was able to scale through to get my good grades 🏃 🏃 🏃 🏃  Thanks to this material.....It helped me go through engineering drawing smoothly. I recommend it for all and sundry</string>
    <string name="joy_testimony7">Smooth Eng103 material is easy to read and understand and I\'d recommend it for every student that wants to be exceptionally good in engineering drawing</string>
    <string name="onyi_testimony8">Smooth\'s ENG 103 material..It is ENG103 made easy.  Very simplified and understandable material. Make use of it and your A is assured and secured.</string>
    <string name="sand_testimony9">I choose to learn from the BEST and in doing so, I came across smooth\'s material, which gave me a great sense of understanding for my engineering drawing.</string>
    <string name="itu_testimony10">It is said that \"knowledge is the key to success\" of which I gained with smooth\'s ENG103 material. Bag your A today with this material and you won\'t regret it.</string>
    <string name="john_testimony11">Creative lines are not just there to lie around, someone has to slice through the dice to make it nice, make your drawings look comprehensive and simple to your lecturers.  I can\'t boast of what I haven\'t seen in this young man maybe it might look overrated but he is a gifted drawer and a practical teacher in engineer drawing, he is willing to bring engineering drawing to the little of your understanding, he is Mr Smooth...</string>
    <string name="itor_testimony12">When it comes to Engineering drawing, there are loads of commentators that talk a good book but SMOOTH helps you make it happen. He has enabled me, coached me and gave me the needed confidence. It\'s engaging readers and commentators alike and bringing our education great results.</string>
    <string name="adu_testimony14">First semester Engine Drawing was actually not difficult for me but where I had the real hell was in my second semester and then I made smooth my good friend 🤗. Through his guidance and tutorials I found out that Engine drawing was actually not difficult and I was able to make a really good grade in the end!</string>
    <string name="vic_testimony15">Smooth is the best Eng103 tutor I\'ve come across in FUTO. He makes the course so simple and understandable. His material is just a proof.</string>
    <string name="lil_testimony16">Back then in my year one, at first, I thought that it would be impossible for me to understand this very course. But then, I came across this material \"THE BEST ENG. DRAWING MATERIAL\" so far. It was so well explained dat even a lay man can understand. It really helped me along side his tutorials that I began to find the course interesting...</string>
</resources>
